[Music]
presente our star product ICICI brood
guaranteed wealth projector get the
power of equity link returns along with
capital protection
[Music]
let's take a look at the key features of
ICICI approve guaranteed wealth
protector it helps you enjoy
equity-linked returns with up to sixty
percent equity exposure
[Music]
it also protects your savings from
market downturns keeping your capital
protected at all times you also have the
freedom to choose your own premium
payment term
what's more you get the benefit of
loyalty additions and wealth boosters
with the help of a life cover you can
secure your family's future last but not
the least you get tax benefits
icici proof guaranteed wealth protector
from ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
viveur of spurious and fictitious or
fraudulent offers ir dia clarifies to
the public that IRDA
does not involve in activities like sale
or any kind of insurance or financial
products nor announce any bonus public
receiving such phone calls are requested
to lodge a police complaint
[Music]